"Did my refractions fade away?"
「私の屈折は消えたのか？」
A thought that haunts me day by day
日々私を悩ませている考え
Like how the foggy air and morning tears
霧のかかった空気や朝の涙が
Dissolve into the atmosphere
大気中に溶けていくように、日々私を悩ませている考え。
Am I just a passing droplet?
私はただ通り過ぎる一滴なのだろうか？
Am I easy to forget?
私は忘れられやすい人間ですか？
Should I keep hoping for your warmth
あなたの温もりを望み続け、
Risk my heart its brittle form
私の心を脆い形に危険にさらし
And keep yearning in the storm?
、嵐の中で憧れ続けるべきでしょうか？
'Cause whenever
だって、いつだって雨の中に
I choose to remain
留まることを選んだら、
To linger in the rain
雨の中で長居する
It will always end the same
いつも同じ結末になるから。
I'll mourn for your embrace
あなたの抱擁を悲しむわ。
Someone will surely fill my place
誰かがきっと私の代わりを務めてくれるわ。
You'll leave me soaked in pain
あなたは私を痛みに浸したまま去っていくの
'Cause that's how it all plays
。だって、すべてがそういうふうに展開するの。
Did I say something in the past?
私は過去に何か言ったかしら？
Or were my problems far too vast?
それとも私の問題はあまりにも大きすぎたのでしょうか?
And now my worries and my evening fears
そして今、私の心配事や夕方の恐怖が
Will be the one to interfere
邪魔をすることになる
Was I just a passing droplet?
私はただ通り過ぎる一滴だったのだろうか？
Was I easy to forget?
私は忘れられやすい人間だったのでしょうか？
Should I keep hoping for your warmth
あなたの温もりを望み続け、
Risk my heart its brittle form
私の心を脆い形に危険にさらし
And keep yearning in the storm?
、嵐の中で憧れ続けるべきでしょうか？ いつ
'Cause whenever
だって
I choose to remain
僕が留まることを選べば
To linger in the rain
雨の中に長居する
It will always end the same
ことは いつも同じ結末を迎える
I'll mourn for your embrace
君の抱擁を嘆くだろう
Someone will surely fill my place
誰かがきっと僕の代わりになるだろう
You'll leave me soaked in pain
君は僕を痛みに浸らせるだろう だって
'Cause that's how it all plays
全てはそういう風に動くんだ
Once I forecasted that someday I'd be replaced
いつか僕に取って代わられると予想していた
This restless hurricane is all too daunting to suppress
落ち着きのないハリケーンは抑えきれないほど恐ろしい
So no more waiting
だからもう待つのはやめて
Anticipating
予想しながら
I'll search for someone else
他の誰かを探すんだ いつだって
'Cause whenever
だっていつでも
I chose to remain
僕が留まることを選べば
To linger in the rain
雨の中に長居することは いつも
I endured a greater pain
より大きな痛みに耐え
I've fallen from your grace
君の恵みから落ちた 君が
I'll miss you, but the hurt's in vain
いなくて寂しいだろうけど その傷は無駄だ
'Cause whenever I-
いつだって
I choose to remain
僕が留まることを選べば
To linger in the rain
雨の中に長居することは
It will always end the same
いつも同じ結末を迎える
I'll mourn for your embrace
君の抱擁を嘆くだろう
Someone will surely fill my place
誰かがきっと僕の代わりになるだろう 君は
You'll leave me soaked in pain
僕を痛みに浸らせるだろう
'Cause that's how it all plays
だって全てはそういう風に動くんだ うん
Yeah, that's how it all plays
、全てはそういう風に動くんだ
♪ I choose to remain ♪
♪ 僕は留まることを選んだ ♪ ♪
♪ To linger in the falling rain ♪
降りしきる雨の中に長居するために ♪
♪ I'll mourn for your embrace ♪
♪ 僕は嘆く あなたの抱擁のために
♪ Someone will surely fill my place ♪
♪♪ 誰かがきっと私の代わりをしてくれるでしょう♪